<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sangam Portfolio</string>
    <string name="about_me">
    Software engineer with 1+ years of experience in software development and with a strong foundation in computer science.\n
    Contributed to enterprise-level systems and backend services focused on reliability, security, and efficiency. Seeking to contribute to teams while growing my skills and gain practical experience.\nI enjoy working in collaborative environments, adapting to new technologies, and turning complex ideas into effective digital solutions.
    \n\n
    Contact: 7210581614\n
    Email: sangamgarg17@gmail.com
</string>
    <string name="quonote"> It is a simple and elegant app that allows users to write, save, and share their favorite quotes. You can also explore a vast collection of quotes from different categories and also download various images. You can add widgets to your home screen with your favorite quotes. Inspirational quotes at your fingertips. It helps to increase productivity.
 This app is built using Android Studio IDE, Kotlin for the backend, Retrofit for API calls, Firebase for data storage and authentication, and XML for layout design. Lottie animations are used to add delightful animations to the user interface.
 I created and published this project on the Google Play Store to enhance my Android development skills and gain real-world experience in app deployment. This hands-on experience has deepened my understanding of Android app development and its practical aspects, enriching my knowledge and skills in the field</string>
    <string name="fitness">Developing a fitness application with a comprehensive suite of fitness functionalities. Integrating standard features alongside innovative machine learning (ML) based fitness games, enhancing user engagement and retention. Implementing a personalized fitness chatbot.</string>
    <string name="bmi">This is my first project using flutter.I made this to explore the world of flutter.The "BMI Calculator App using Flutter" is a mobile application designed to help users calculate their Body Mass Index (BMI) quickly and easily. BMI is a measure of body fat based on an individual\'s weight and height. This app empowers users to monitor and understand their BMI, offering insights into their overall health status.</string>
    <string name="ar">This application revolutionizes the way kids visualize and learn things. Utilizing AR, the app displays animated animals, plants ,birds ,etc. with their respective sound and category. which will help kids to visualize the nature in their surrounding.
 This app is built using Android Studio IDE, Kotlin for the backend, Firebase for data storage and authentication, and XML for layout design. Google ARCORE for AR implementation.</string>
    <string name="social">This application is an online platform used to build and develop relation between peoples and modified the way people communicate.
This website permit users to upload pics, upload multimedia content material  or alternate the profile and   sound of profiles , weblog posts , comments and sharing contact listing.Users can choose who can view, edit and add to their friend list ,and so on ,to preserve  their privacy on social media platform.
It provides ways to Users to interact online with people with similar interests for social purposes  Like, Dislike , Online comments ,digital photographs post submissions are all possible.

</string>
    <string name="more_about_me"><u>More About Me</u></string>
    <string name="talentitan"><b>TALEN TITAN PRIVATE LIMITED \nRemote Oct 2023 – Mar 2024\nAndroid Developer Intern\n
• Developed and enhanced Android app features by integrating external data sources and RESTful APIs, optimizing data management with in memory database, leading to a 30% improvement in data processing efficiency.\n
• Implemented in-app ads that contributed to a 15% increase in app-generated revenue.\n
• Diagnosed and resolved software bugs, performance issues, and performed debugging to ensure high-quality performance, delivering interactive and user-friendly interfaces.
    </b></string>


    <string name="tcs"><b>TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES\nMumbai, India May 2025 – Present\nJava Developer: State Bank of India, CKYC (Central Know Your Customer) Project\n
• Optimized customer account lookups, reducing repeated server calls by 40% and improving average response time by 30% during branch customer verification workflows.\n
• Implemented SQL query optimization and indexing strategies that reduced data retrieval time by over 25%, improving the performance of high-volume extraction jobs.\n
• Contributed to redundant code optimization and modularization, reducing maintenance overhead and improving code reusability.
    </b></string>


    <string name="isg">FREELANCE DEVELOPER – Remote Apr 2024 – June 2024\nJava and Android Developer\n
• Architected and developed a seat booking application, incorporating secure payments and QR check-ins, facilitating 100+ successful reservations within the first month of deployment across libraries and gyms.\n
• Designed user flows and system architecture for a smooth user experience —boosted task efficiency by 25%.\n
• Reduced check-in time by 50% through efficient QR scanning implementation.\n
• Applied Clean Architecture, Design Patterns and Security Measures to create a scalable, testable, and maintainable codebase, and well-structured APIs that simplified frontend integration and reduced development effort.</string>
    <string name="java_developer_nkotlin_java_spring_boot">Java Developer @TCS\nSoftware Engineer\nKotlin, Java, Spring Boot</string>

</resources>